

TASHA JAVALERA

WEB DEVELOPER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

PERSONAL PROFILE

years of exploration to find an industry that I will be happy to build a career in, just like many others I suppose. What compels me the most about a career in Web Development and Graphic Design is the combine use of design and technology to create visually stunning tools and websites for our modern society. I worked at Verizon Wireless during the boom of the smartphone and have seen first hand the strides that technology has made and that experience has instilled in me a passion for quality online content.

As a "creative" it's taken some

CONTACT

- 1787 W. 900 N. SLC, UT 84116
- mrs.javalera@gmail.com
- 801-719-7412

SKILLS

- Exceptional communication and networking skills
- Successful working in a team environment, as well as independently
- The ability to work under pressure and multi-task
- The ability to follow instructions and deliver quality results on time.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Northridge Learning Center/ Dorius Academy

FEBUARY 2018- AUGUST 2019, JANUARY 2020- PRESENT

I work as an advocate helping high school students make up, or get ahead in credits by setting them up in Northridge's program. Student's would complete lessons and assignments in a packet as well as Canvas then come into the office to complete a final exam. My day to day mainly consisted of sales, customer service, data entry, inventory management and record keeping. More recently I have been given charge of a project to update tests and quizzes in canvas with pre-written questions. I am also submitting work to my marketing manager for feedback to hopefully be premoted to the marketing team as a graphic designer.



TASHA JAVALERA

WEB DEVELOPER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

EDUCATION

Salt Lake Community College Certificate of completion 2020

REFERENCES

Salt Lake Community College Certificate of completion 2020

PORTFOLIO

here are some of my graphic designs:



WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

Northridge Learning Center/Dorius Academy

FEBUARY 2018- AUGUST 2019, JANUARY 2020- PRESENT

I work as an advocate helping high school students make up, or get ahead in credits by setting them up in Northridge's program. Student's would complete lessons and assignments in a packet as well as Canvas then come into the office to complete a final exam. My day to day mainly consisted of sales, customer service, data entry, inventory management and record keeping. More recently I have been given charge of a project to update tests and quizzes in canvas with pre-written questions. I am also submitting work to my marketing manager for feedback to hopefully be promoted to the marketing team as a graphic designer.

Small Business Owner

JJULY 2017- PRESENT: TASHA'S GRAPHICS BY DESIGN & TASHA'S BOUTIQUE

Owning my own small online business has given me a starting background in marketing, business development, and project management. Most importantly though I believe, owning my own business has given me a drive for inovation and improvement that I can apply to any aspect of my life whether personal or professional.



TASHA JAVALERA

WEB DEVELOPER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

MODEST POP





SISTERS Selling Stuff

WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

Verizon Wireless

From 2008 to 2012 I was a customer service agent and handled consumer wireless accounts. I would take incoming calls requests to manage their account such as billing plan maintenance, sales, technical support and inquiries all while managing my efficiency and sales numbers.

In 2012 I was promoted to Business and Government Operations. My responsibilities included servicing corporate and business accounts with hundreds of lines to manage their billing, sales, advanced technical support, maintenance, detailed reports, online tools and account security.